http://www.dcc.edu/about/website-privacy-policy.aspx

Header Two
Home
About Delgado
Website Privacy Policy
About Delgado HomeChancellor's WelcomeMission, Vision and ValuesChancellor's Social Justice MessageLocationsFast FactsHistorySocial MediaContact UsWebsite Privacy PolicyCommunity PartnersAccreditationDisclaimersAnnual Public NotificationPhoto GalleryDelgado Pride News Radio Show Archive
Website Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, respond to a survey,
or fill out a form.
When registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name,
email address, mailing address, phone number, or credit card information. You may,
however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you from the website may be used in one of
the following ways:
To personalize your website experience(Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)
To improve our website(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and
feedback we receive from you.)
To send periodic emails(The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you
information and updates that you have asked for. If you decide to opt-in to our website
mailing list, you will receive emails that may include news, updates, related product
or service information, etc.)
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we
include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal
information when you place an order or access your personal information through our
website.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is
transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment
gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special
access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a website transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security
numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.
Do we use cookies?
Yes, cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your
device's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites
or service providers' systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain
information.
Our website uses cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits
and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can
offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party
service providers to assist us in better understanding our website visitors. These
service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf
except to help us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is
being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like
most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function
properly.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable
information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating
our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree
to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies,
or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable
visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or
other uses.
Third-party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party links on our
website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We
therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these
linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome
any feedback about these sites.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection
Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website,
products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or
older.
Online Website Privacy Policy Only
This online website privacy policy applies only to information collected through our
website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our website, you consent to our website privacy policy.
Changes to Our Website Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our website privacy policy, we will post those changes on this
page, and/or update the Website Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified August 27, 2020.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us.
©
